Ashuha Arseniy

Moscow, Russia • 🔊 +7-965-178-2915 • ⊠ ars.ashuha@gmail.com • 🕏 ars-ashuha • k arsashuha • 🗖 ars-ashuha



Summary

I am a second year Master Student at MIPT, I do research at Bayes Group under supervision of prof. Dmitry Vetrov. My research is focused on Bayesian regularization of deep neural nets. At MIPT I work as a teacher assistant for some Machine Learning courses. Also, I am an irregular student of Yandex School of Data Analysis.

Skills: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Bayesian ML, Python, Hadoop, Hive, Linux, English (B2)

Education

2011 - 2015 Bachelor, Computer Science, Bauman Moscow State Technical University, GPA: 3.7/5.0 Thesis Identification of unique kernels in topic models, Supervisor: N. Loukachevitch (MSU)

2015 - 2017 Master, Machine Learning, Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, GPA: ?/5.0 Thesis Regularization of Deep Neural Nets, Supervisor: Prof. D. Vetrov (HSE), A. Dral (MIPT)

2015 - 2017 Irregular Student, Machine Learning, Yandex School of Data Analysis, GPA: 4.8/5.0 Result Six courses were passed and the favorites are Bayesian ML, Deep Learning, Machine Learning

Teaching

- 2016 Now: Teacher Assistant, University Course at MIPT, Machine Learning (parts 1,2), ml-mipt.github.io (RU)
- 2016 Now: Teacher Assistant, Additional Course at MIPT, Machine Learning in Action, vk.com/ml_in_action (RU)
- 2016 Now: Preparing and checking some tasks for several courses like DL, BMML, LA in SDA, MSU, HSE

Experience

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016 3 month

Yandex, Moscow — Intern at Music Deep Learning Group (E. Krofto) • Searching similar tracks and building recommendation features using DNN

Yandex

RAMBLER&Co

Dec 2013 - Feb 2016

Rambler, Moscow — R&D Engineer at ML Group (A. Gorokhov, P. Klemenkov)

2 year 1 month p/t

- Improving the quality of classification users using browser history
- Recommendations system for the news posts on rambler.ru
- Optimization performance of users classification
- Application of topic models to building users features

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013 Rambler, Moscow — Intern at Search Group (M. Karpenko)

3 month

• Users query classification to show a mixing in search results

RAMBLER&Co

Publications

Dmitry Molchanov, Arseniy Ashuha and Dmitry Vetrov

Dropout-based Automatic Relevance Determination Bayesian Deep Learning Workshop, Neural Information Processing Systems 2016

Arseniy Ashuha and Natalia Loukachevitch

Bigramm Anchor Words Topic Model International Conference on Image Analysis, Social Networks and Texts 2016